luckygunner.com 2019-06-15

# Privacy Policy

  1. Our Commitment To Your Privacy
  2. Our Commitment To Data Security
  3. The Personal Information We Collect 
  4. Sharing Your Personal Information
  5. How To Edit Your Personal Information or Contact Us

* * *

### Our Commitment To Your Privacy

We value our customers and their privacy. We won't follow you around the web to collect information about your browsing activities, and we won't retarget you with ads on other sites. The limited information we do collect will be used to serve you and it will be handled in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy may be amended from time to time, and updated versions will be posted here.

To use our checkout system, you'll need to provide certain "Personal Information" (categories described below). The Personal Information you provide is used to ensure efficient processing of your orders and to otherwise assist our staff in making sure that you have a pleasant experience with LuckyGunner.com. We will not give, sell, rent, or loan any Personal Information to any third party, unless we believe that we are legally required to do so, you authorize us to do so, or we believe we need to in order to protect our business or the public. 

### Our Commitment To Data Security

We handle your Personal Information with utmost care. Our entire site is PCI-DSS compliant, and our checkout process is fully secured with strong SSL encryption. When you place your order online, your credit card information passes directly from your browswer to the payment processor. It's never seen by, or stored within, our system. Further, subject to the below, no third parties can collect your Personal Information when you use our site. 

### The Personal Information We Collect

LuckyGunner.com's checkout system requires you to provide the following Personal Information: your name, your billing and shipping address, your email address, your telephone number, and your credit card information. Some states may require us by law to collect additional information, like an identification card. Please be sure to input your information accurately so that we can better serve you. We only collect this Personal Information if you enter the information into our checkout process or if you create a customer account. We do not collect Personal Information if you're simply browsing our site. 

### Sharing Your Personal Information

To process your order, some of your Personal Information will be entrusted with a small group of trusted partners, including carriers like FedEx or UPS; our credit card processor; our friends at the warehouse; and other support partners. We also share your Personal Information with our third party digital marketing partner who helps with email outreach. We only give these folks the minimum amount of information they need to play their part in our well-oiled machine. We do not share your Personal Information with any marketing or advertising companies, and we don't use any retargeting efforts to follow you while you browse other sites on the web. Like many ecommerce sites, we use Google Analytics and Google Analytics Advertising Features (“GA”) to gather information on parts of our website, with the goal of better serving you by improving user experience, product offering, and the quality of the site. Information collected through GA doesn't include any of your Personal Information, but it may include data like age, gender, and interests. No Personal Information is collected. GA uses first-party and third-party cookies to learn about a site visitor's shopping preferences, as well as to collect data about how visitors use the site. The cookies are linked to our site, and we only use that data to understand how visitors use the site and how to better serve you. By using our site, you agree to our use of such information, and you further agree to GA’s terms found here: <http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners>. You may opt out of GA by adjusting your settings on Google Ad Preferences, by visting the [GA opt-out page](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/ "GA opt-out page") and installing the add-on for your browser, or by following the steps on the [NAI’s opt-out page](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#!/ "NAI’s opt-out page") We do not modify tracking behavior in response to Do Not Track Signals. 

### How To Edit Your Personal Information or Contact Us

If you create a customer account with us, you can edit your Personal Information simply by logging into your account and making your desired changes. If you'd like to opt out of newsletters and other emails, just select the unsubscribe option at the bottom of the message. Should you have other questions or concerns, please call us at (800) 317-9506 or send a friendly email to [customerservice@luckygunner.com](mailto:customerservice@luckygunner.com). We look forward to assisting you. 

* * *

Back To Top ^
